COPYWRITER

Yesenia Ortiz Franco

PROFILE

Experienced Collections Specialist bringing 3-years of success in sales and service positions. Eager to take on new role with long-term growth and advancement potential. Dynamic problem solver with first-rate skills in building relationships and resolving problems.

Trustworthy and dedicated Barista with 3 years of experience serving customers and operating register. Talented at correctly taking order information and serving to customers quickly. Cheerful when assisting customers with requests and meeting special needs.

EXPERIENCE

WAREHOUSE ASSOCIATE, AMAZON; NORTH LAS VEGAS, NEVADA - 2020-2021

- •Worked safely around moving machinery.
- Prepared orders for shipment by systematically picking, packing and labeling merchandise.

Wrapped pallets in shrink wrap prior to loading.

- Used hand-held scanners and physical logs to accurately track item movements.
- Listened closely during team meetings to gain complete understanding of duties required for each shift, completing priority tasks first.
- Received and processed warehouse orders using handheld scanner.
- Checked packages and merchandise for damage and notified vendors.
- · Labeled and accurately moved customer orders to meet shipment timetables and minimize errors.
- · Consistently lifted materials weighing as much as 50 pounds.

BARISTA, PROTEIN HOUSE; LAS VEGAS, NEVADA - 2019-2020

- · Pleasantly interacted with customers during hectic periods to promote fun, positive environment.
- Cleaned counters, machines, utensils and seating areas daily.
- Maintained regular and consistent attendance and punctuality.
- · Trained new team members with positive reinforcement and respectful, encouraging coaching.
- · Maintained supply levels in counter and customer areas to meet typical demands.
- · Prioritized drink requests while managing interruptions.
- · Pleasantly interacted with customers during hectic periods to promote fun, positive environment.
- · Recommended products based on solid understanding of individual customer needs and preferences.

SERVICE TEAM& KITCHEN STAFF, PANDA EXPRESS; LAS VEGAS, NEVADA - 2019-19

- · Maintained compliance with company policies and procedures for food safety, sanitation and quality.
- · Limited portion sizes and used garnishes to control food costs.

- · Maintained clean, sanitized and well-organized food preparation zones.
- · Wiped counters and sanitized equipment to maintain clean food prep and dining areas.
- Strictly followed sanitation and food safety guidelines as required by regulatory agencies and company.
- Checked completed orders for accuracy and bagged meals for easy carrying.
- · Assisted customers by answering questions and fulfilling requests.
- Assisted cashier team with resolving problems and maintaining efficiency.
- · Quickly and accurately counted drawers at start and end of each shift.

EDUCATION

Rancho High-school, North Las Vegas, Nevada – Diploma, 2019

SKILLS

- · Order Picking and Processing
- · Cleaning
- · Warehouse Environment Safety
- · Box Lifting
- POS Systems
- Drawer Management
- · Money handling
- Customer assistance
- · Cleaning and sanitizing
- · Product knowledge
- Order taking
- Customer Service
- · Multitasking abilities
- · Teamwork skills
- · Critical thinking